A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6 FA459
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Vice Presidential, 6
  - Contact Sheets, 1973-1977; 1
    - G1735 - Sadat luncheon at Capitol; press conference, 1975 November 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1736 - Press conference; gifts from Sadat, 1975 November 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1737 - Press conference, room 450, EOB, 1975 November 6; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1738 - G1743 - Austin, Texas, 1975 November 11; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1744 - Anwar Sadat in Houston, 1975 November 11; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1745 - Nancy Dickerson, 1975 November 12; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1746 - Alexander Haig; Rep. Guyer (OH) and Dr. Kim, 1975 November 13; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1747 - Dr. Charles Malik; Alexander Haig, 1975 November 13; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1748 - G1752 - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and St. Cloud, Minnesota, 1975 November 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 19, Volume 10)
    - G1753 - G1755 - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and St. Cloud, Minnesota, 1975 November 15; Color (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1756 - G1758 - Lincolnshire, Illinois, 1975 November 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1759 - G1760 - Kansas City, Missouri, 1975 November 15; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1761 - G1766 - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1975 November 18; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1767 - Sen. Mathias (MD); Council of 100, 1975 November 19; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1768 - Council of 100, 1975 November 19; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1769 - Sen. Mathias (MD); reception for rep. Rhodes (AZ); Council of 100, 1975 November 19; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1770 - Trip to Spain, 1975 November 27; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1771 - G1780 - Trip to Spain, 1975 November 27; Color (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1781 - G1784 - Wichita, Kansas, 1975 November 21; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1785 - Trip to Spain, 1975 November 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1786 - Trip to Spain, 1975 November 22; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1787 - G1789 - Trip to Spain, 1975 November 22; Color (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1790 - New VP seal and flag presentation; Federal Women's Award, 1975 December 4; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1791 - New VP seal and flag presentation; Reps. Cleveland (NH) and Jones (AL); Ed Gee; General Clarke and Donna Mitchell; Federal Women's Award, 1975 December 4; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1792 - National Association of Manufacturers, New York, NY, 1975 December 5; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1793 - National Association of Manufacturers, New York, 1975 December 5; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1794 - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1975 December 5; Color (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1795 - G1796 - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1975 December 5; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1797 - G1799 - Los Angeles, California - domestic forum, 1975 December 9; Black and White (Box 5, Folder 20, Volume 10)
    - G1800 - G1804 - Los Angeles, California - domestic forum, 1975 December 9; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1805 - Council on Environmental Quality; Walt Disney World Showcase briefing; Republican Congressional Boosters Club, 1975 December 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1806 - Council on Environmental Quality, 1975 December 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1807 - G1814 - Houston, Texas, 1975 December 11; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1815 - G1817 - Nashville, Tennessee, 1975 December 11; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1818 - G1821 - Staff party, Naval Observatory, 1975 December 16; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1822 - Carleton Smith; John Oakes; Carole Richards, 1975 December 16; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1823 - Meeting with freshmen congressmen, 1975 December 16; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1824 - Press conference at White House; Domestic Council staff, 1975 December 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1825 - G1826 - President's safety award presentation, 1975 December 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1827 - Press conference at White House; Domestic Council staff; Bern Shanley, 1975 December 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1828 - G1831 - Secret Service Christmas party, Naval Observatory, 1975 December 17; Color (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1832 - Yigal Allon, Israeli Foreign Minister, 1976 January 7; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1833 - Yigal Allon, Israeli Foreign Minister, 1976 January 7; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1834 - Jon Howe; Abe Levine; John McCone; Dr. Annmarie Walsh, 1976 January 7; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1835 - Trade commission; Dick Allinson; Robert West and Arthur Spitzer, 1976 January 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1836 - National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1976 January 14; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1837 - National Council of Farmer Cooperatives; Japanese TV interview, 1976 January 14; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1838 - National Council of Farmer Cooperatives; science advisory group; Japanese TV interview, 1976 January 14; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1839 - Presentation of Henry Wallace bust, National Portrait Gallery, 1976 January 21; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1840 - Kohn Lawrence; Sol Kohler, 1976 January 15; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1841 - Salem College convocation, Salem, West Virginia, 1976 January 26; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1842 - Service Wives Club, Bolling AFB; Salem College convocation, Salem, West Virginia, 1976 January 26; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1843 - Bruce Clark; Service Club Wives; Salem College convocation, Salem, West Virginia, 1976 January 26; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1844 - Morrison Red Tucker; Willy Williams; Salem College convocation, Salem, West Virginia, 1976 January 26; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1845 - Veneman, Zarb, Wallison; Drs. Walsh and Wade; Prime Minister Rabin; Bipartisan Leadership meeting, 1976 January 27; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1846 - Salem College convocation, Salem, West Virginia; Prime Minister Rabin; Bipartisan Leadership meeting, 1976 January 27; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1847 - Westchester County Republican Committee dinner; PFC reception, 1976 January 29; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1848 - Westchester County Republican Committee dinner, 1976 January 29; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1849 - Westchester County Republican Committee dinner; PFC reception, 1976 January 29; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1850 - Westchester County Republican Committee dinner, 1976 January 29; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 21, Volume 11)
    - G1851 - G1855 - Dearborn, Michigan, 1976 January 30; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1856 - Revenue sharing meeting, Cabinet room, 1976 February 3; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1857 - Fred Clark, Donna Mitchell, Joe Moore and Jim Smith; revenue sharing meeting, 1976 February 3; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1858 - Senate Government Operations Committee testimony; Senate youth program award luncheon, 1976 February 4; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1859 - Senate Government Operations Committee testimony, 1976 February 4; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1860 - Senate Government Operations Committee testimony; Senate youth program award luncheon; Ambassador Martin Hillenbrand, 1976 February 4; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1861 - Senate Government Operations Committee testimony; Senate youth program award luncheon, 1976 February 4; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1862 - G1864 - National Endowment of the Arts; Northeast Republican Leadership Conference, 1976 February 6; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1865 - Governor's Mansion, Albany, New York (copy), 1976 February 9; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1866 - Colorado bicentennial presentation; Frank Mastro painting presentation; Atomic Industrial Forum; Japanese Diet, 1976 February 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1867 - Colorado bicentennial presentation; Atomic Industrial Forum, 1976 February 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1868 - Atomic Industrial Forum, 1976 February 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1869 - Apollo-Soyuz flight flag; Happy and Carol, 1976 February 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1870 - Susan Herter; Apollo-Soyuz flight flag, 1976 February 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1871 - G1876 - Lexington, Kentucky, 1976 February 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1877 - Arthur Burns; Amory Houston, Jr.; Todd Hullin; Mrs. Henry Brandon, 1976 February 18; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1878 - Todd Hullin; White House fellows, 1976 February 18; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1879 - G1881 - National Press Club luncheon, 1976 February 19; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1882 - G1886 - Michigan State Republican Committee Bicentennial Day dinner, Lansing, Michigan, 1976 February 20; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1887 - American Association for the Advancement of Science; National Governors Club lunch; Dr. John Hannah, 1976 February 24; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1888 - Herman Kahn, Leon Martel, Thomas Pepper; National Governors Club lunch; Dr. John Hannah; Sen. Proxmire (WI); Zarb; Wallison, 1976 February 24; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1889 - National Governors Club lunch, Statler Hilton Hotel, 1976 February 24; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1890 - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Boston, MA, 1976 February 24; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1891 - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Boston, MA, 1976 February 24; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1892 - Domestic Council Associate Director Arthur Fletcher swearing-in ceremony, 1976 February 25; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1893 - Domestic Council Associate Director Arthur Fletcher swearing-in ceremony; Bill Matney and ABC film crew; Rep. Chisholm (NY), 1976 February 25; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1894 - Arthur Fletcher; Thad Garrett, 1976 February 25; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1895 - Bicentennial Bishops and Connectional Council award dinner, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 February 25; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1896 - Rep. Chisholm (NY); Bicentennial Bishops Connectional Council award dinner, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 February 25; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1897 - Republican Eagles; BBC taping; military awards ceremony, 1976 February 27; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1898 - Rep. Heckler (MA) and Elly Petersen; Sgt. Bill Moore; Chief Dick Williams; Gov. Shafer, 1976 February 27; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1899 - Republican National Committee reception, Naval Observatory, 1976 February 27; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 22, Volume 11)
    - G1900 - Cannon, Gov. Shafer, Meyer; Walker, Zarb, Veneman, Wallison; Water Quality Commission, 1976 March 2; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1901 - Veneman; Sanford Unger; Water Quality Commission, 1976 March 2; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1902 - Gas Appliance Manufacturers; Sen. Pell (RI); Alfred Pooer, 1976 March 3; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1903 - Sen. Pell (RI); National Academy of Design medal; Clarence Streit; Shiela Mosler, 1976 March 3; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1905 - Dean Alfange and Cannon; Gov. Shafer birthday; B?nai B?rith Women biennial convention (Mrs. Rockefeller), 1976 March 9; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1906 - Carla Hills, Dean Alfange and Cannon; B?nai B?rith Women biennial convention (Mrs. Rockefeller), 1976 March 3; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1907 - Vice President and Mrs. Rockefeller, 1976 March 11; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1908 - Mrs. Rockefeller, 1976 March 11; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1909 - Sens. Brooke (MA), Packwood (OR), Helms (NC), Tower (TX), and Garn (NV); National Energy Council; Ambassador Montiero (Singapore), 1976 March 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1910 - Sens. Brooke (MA), Packwood (OR), Helms (NC), Tower (TX), and Garn (NV); Sen. Byrd (VA); National Energy Council; Jass McMullen, Australian Broadcasting Commission, 1976 March 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1911 - National Energy Council, 1976 March 10; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1912 - G1913 - Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1976 March 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1914 - Joseph Canzeri and Chuck McGuire; Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1976 March 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1915 - Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1976 March 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1916 - West Point presentation to Capt. Jon Howe; Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1976 March 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1917 - Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1976 March 12; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1918 - Sec. and Mrs. Kissinger, Naval Observatory; Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1976 March 12; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1919 - Saudi Arabian Ambassador; Arthur Spitzer; John Gardner; Pakistan Ambassador Yaqub Khan; New Zealand Ambassador White; Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 11; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1920 - Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1921 - Republican members of the House Banking and Currency subcommittee on economic stabilization; Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1922 - Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1923 - Republican members of the House Banking and Currency subcommittee on economic stabilization; Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1924 - Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 17; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1925 - Chicago, Illinois, 1976 March 17; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1926 - Senate Joint Economic Committee; Mrs. Peacock (Australia) and Sen. Baker (TN); Ambassador Parkinson and New Zealand Foreign Affairs Secretary Alan Renouf, 1976 March 18; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1927 - Under Secretary Charles Robinson, Alan Atherton and Rutherford Poats, 1976 March 18; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1928 - Senate Joint Economic Committee; Capitol subway with Sen. Goldwater (AZ); Mrs. Peacock (Australia) and Sen. Baker (TN), 1976 March 18; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1929 - State gifts, 1976 March 18; Black and White (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1930 - G1936 - Tunis, Tunisia, 1976 March 20; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1937 - Paris, France, 1976 March 21; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1938 - G1941 - Tours, France, 1976 March 21; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1942 - Tunis, Tunisia; Tours, France, 1976 March 21; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1943 - G1949 - Paris, France, 1976 March 21; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1950 - G1953 - Kish Island, Iran, 1976 March 24; Color (Box 6, Folder 23, Volume 12)
    - G1954 - G1959 - Isfahan, Iran, 1976 March 25; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1960 - G1966 - Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 1976 March 27; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1967 - Kish Island, Iran, 1976 March 26; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1968 - Kish Island, Iran, 1976 March 26; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1969 - Shiraz, Iran; Malaysia, 1976 March 26; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1970 - Singapore, 1976 March 28; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1971 - G1973 - Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia; Singapore, 1976 March 28; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1974 - G1980 - Bali, 1976 March 29; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1981 - Singapore, 1976 March 29; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1982 - G1986 - Canberra, Australia, 1976 March 30; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1987 - Wellington, New Zealand, 1976 March 31; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1988 - G1990 - Sidney, Australia, 1976 March 31; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1991 - Wellington, New Zealand, 1976 April 1; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1992 - Wellington, New Zealand, 1976 April 1; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G1993 - G1999 - Wellington, New Zealand, 1976 April 2; Color (Box 6, Folder 24, Volume 12)
    - G2000 - Tahiti, 1976 April 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2001 - Tahiti; Air Force 2 crew, 1976 April 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2002 - Tahiti, 1976 April 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2003 - Tahiti, 1976 April 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2004 - Air Force 2 crew, 1976 April 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2005 - Sidney, Australia, 1976 April 1; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2006 - Sidney, Australia, 1976 April 1; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2007 - G2009 - LBJ Memorial Grove dedication, 1976 April 6; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2010 - Energy independence meeting, 1976 April 7; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2011 - State gifts, 1976 April 7; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2012 - Lunch with Sens. Humphrey (MN), Long (LA), Talmadge (GA), and Randolph (WV); Veneman, Wallison and Canfield; Americans for Energy Independence, 1976 April 7; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2012a - Lunch with Sens. McGee (WY), Byrd (VA), Inouye (HI), and Hollings (SC); Zarb, Veneman, and Wallison; Gov. Ray (IA) and group, 1976 April 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2013 - American For Energy Independence; lunch with Sens. McGee (WY), Inouye (HI), Byrd (VA), and Hollings (SC); Zarb, Veneman and Wallison; WETA interview, 1976 April 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2013a - Lunch with Sens. Humphrey (MN), Long (LA), Talmadge (GA) and Randolph (WV); Greek Ambassador Alexandrakis, 1976 April 7; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2014 - Americans For Energy Independence, 1976 April 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2014a - Appearance before the House Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 April 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2015 - Appearance before the House Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs; Gerald Parsky; Club of Rome, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 April 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2016 - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 April 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2017 - Appearance before the House Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs; Gerald Parsky; Club of Rome, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 April 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2021 - Rogers Morton; Emmet Hughes; Christian Herter, Jr., swearing-in, 1976 April 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2022 - Sens. Stevens (AK), Brock (TN), Beall (MD), Buckley (NY), Roth (DE), Stafford (VT), and Taft (OH); Werner Von Braun, Charles Hewitt, Jason Stearn, Christian Herter, Jr., 1976 April 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2023 - Des Moines, Iowa, 1976 April 14; Black and White (Box 7, Frame 25, Volume 13)
    - G2024 - J. Scott, K. C. Star; Des Moines, Iowa, 1976 April 14; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2025 - G2027 - Des Moines, Iowa, 1976 April 14; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2028 - G2031 - Atlanta, Georgia, 1976 April 15; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2032 - Des Moines, Iowa; Atlanta, Georgia, 1976 April 15; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2033 - Argentine Ambassador Fasquez and Jorge Borges; President's Personnel Interchange Program dinner, 1976 April 20; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2034 - James Cary, Ed Pernie, Ed Nielen (Copley Newspapers); monthly chartbooks meeting; Werner Von Braun, Hugh Downs, Charles Hewitt, Jason Stearn, Dick Allison, 1976 April 21; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2035 - Argentine Ambassador Fasquez and Jorge Borges; Phil Shebecoff (NY Times); Max Kampelman; James Petrie; Jack Bassler, Robert Saltzman, 1976 April 20; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2036 - Greener; White House press photographers, 1976 April 22; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2037 - Marcus Rowden and Carlton Kammerer; White House Press Photographers dinner, 1976 April 22; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2038 - White House Press Photographers dinner, 1976 April 22; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2039 - White House Press Photographers dinner, 1976 April 22; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2040 - Gov. Shafer portraits, 1976 April 26; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2041 - Joint Chiefs Of Staff; Yugoslavian Parliamentarians; American Oceanic Organization dinner, 1976 April 28; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2042 - American Oceanic Organization dinner, 1976 April 28; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2043 - Reps. Dingell (MI) and Reuss (WI), Zarb, Wallison, Veneman; National Leadership Conference on American Health Policy, 1976 April 28; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2044 - Betty Crocker scholarships; Reps. Dingell (MI) and Reuss (WI), Zarb, Wallison, Veneman; California agricultural leaders; National Leadership Conference on American Health Policy, 1976 April 28; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2045 - G2047 - George Washington Inauguration Day program, 1976 April 30; Color (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2048 - G2050 - San Francisco, California, 1976 May 4; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 25, Volume 13)
    - G2051 - G2053 - Los Angeles, California, 1976 May 5; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)